Minahil Akhtar

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan



minahilakhtar2235@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/minahil-akhtar

Summary

I am a MERN Stack and WordPress Developer with experience in modern technologies such as React.JS, Redux, Node.JS, Express.js, REST APIs, MongoDB, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap. I am passionate about what I'm doing and see every task as a challenge and an opportunity to get better.

My portfolio site minahilakhtar.github.io/cv

My Personal Website https://minahilakhtar.com

Experience



📉 Frontend Developer

Chingu

Aug 2023 - Present (2 months)

I have worked on chingu as a Front-end Developer at Chingu, collaborating closely with a dynamic team of developers on a wide range of projects.

p Frontend Web Developer

Upwork

Jan 2021 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Frontend Developer

Bulls Orbit

Mar 2022 - Apr 2023 (1 year 2 months)

I have worked at Bulls Orbit as a Front end developer There I Completed a lot of tasks related to web development.

Frontend Web Developer

Frontend Mentor

Mar 2021 - Jan 2022 (11 months)

https://www.frontendmentor.io/profile/minahilakhtar

Education

ĕ Zero To Mastery Academy

Feb 2020 - Mar 2021

- Asean Online Education AOE
- M Army Public School (APSACS)
- (A) freeCodeCamp

Licenses & Certifications

- Digital Marketing DigiSkills.pk 6727RGTPQ
- Facebook Ads Asean Online Education AOE 192816199672
- **CSS & JavaScript Certification Course** Udemy UC-724f3a84-6e24-4713-9e0f-14228640c28e
- Google Ads Search Certification
 49530046
- Digital Marketing Master Class FEMPROW
- **The Fundamental Of Digital Maketing** Google Digital Garage WTP FPL EEV
- JavaScript Essential Training LinkedIn AVsUkDaaMFz2jlx0L_tjEQ2ayl7l
- in HTML Essential Training LinkedIn Addl3VLWTGsp1hdEL6R35_6m2Avr
- CSS Essential Training LinkedIn
 AY26hCblGorlqYc30aeNwOaiuwLE

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Bootstrap (Framework) • Tailwind CSS • React.js • MongoDB • Node.js • REST APIs • WordPress